save-a-lot.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy | Save A Lot

## **SAVE-A-LOT PRIVACY POLICY**

### **This policy was Posted on December 9th, 2016 and is effective immediately.**

We value the privacy of our customers’ information and we are always striving to make our customer experience better.  We prepared this Privacy Policy to describe our information practices and, in particular, how we collect, use and share the Personal Information that we gather through our Site, as defined below.  If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our information practices, please contact us through the options provided below. 

**BY USING OUR SITE, YOU CONSENT TO THE INFORMATION PRACTICES AND OTHER TERMS AS DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY.   **

Who We Are

Independent Stores

How We Collect and Use Personal Information

Additional Uses of Personal Information

How We Share and Disclose Personal Information

Your Ad Choices

Children’s Privacy

How to Access or Update Your Information

Links to Other Websites

Updates to this Privacy Policy

Managing Communication Preferences

How to Contact Us

### **Who We Are**

We are Moran Foods, LLC, operating under the brand name SAVE-A-LOT (“Save-A-Lot,” “we,” or “us”). This Privacy Policy applies to the websites owned and operated by us that link to this Privacy Policy (we call these the “Sites”).

### **Independent Stores**

We also have licensing and wholesale relationships with a network of independent retailers that independently own and operate their grocery stores (“ **Independent Stores** ”), but who license the use of our brand name and/or use our wholesale distribution network.  

Some Independent Stores may operate their own websites or mobile applications, separate and apart from the Site. Those websites and mobile applications are not operated by us and are not subject to this Privacy Policy. Please review the privacy policy posted on those websites or mobile applications to understand the applicable information practices.

### **How We Collect and Use Personal Information**

When we use the term “ **Personal Information** ” in this Privacy Policy, we mean any information that we directly associate with a specific person, or that reasonably can be used to identify a specific person.  For example, this includes your name, home address, phone number, email address, birthday and any other information that we tie to these elements.

Personal Information does not include “aggregated information,” which is information that we collect about a group or category of persons or services.  It also does not include “de-identified information,” which is information from which we or our agents have removed information that can be used to specifically identify a person. This Privacy Policy does not apply to our collection, use, or disclosure of aggregated or de-identified information.

We collect the following types of Personal Information when you use our Site:

**1\. Information You Provide**

We collect Personal Information you provide, for example when you enter the information into form fields on our Sites or enroll in our Smart Shopper Club program.  For example, we may collect:

  * contact information, such as your name, home address, and email address, which we use to communicate with you and authenticate you as a user;
  * demographic information, including age, product preferences, preferred store location and other interests and likes, which we use to better understand and analyze our customer population, support our operations including inventory and product management, to deliver relevant offers and ads, and to improve our products and services including the Site;
  * communications preferences, including marketing preferences, which we  use to manage how we engage with you;
  * application information related to becoming an owner of an Independent Store;
  * the content of inquiries you make.

**2\. Information Collected Automatically**

We use various technologies to collect other types of data that do not directly reveal your identity (“ **Other Information** ”).  If we associate Other Information with Personal Information, we will treat the combined information as Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

These technologies include the following:

**Logging Functionality:** As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include IP addresses, browser type, internet service provider, referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp and/or clickstream data.  We generally only use this data for purposes such as security, fraud detection, and protecting our rights.

**Cookies and Other Data Collection Technologies:** We and third parties we work with use cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies to manage our websites and email messages and to collect and track information about you and your activities online over time and across different websites.  In addition, we use local shared objects (or Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your preferences and how you interact with the Site. These technologies help us to recognize you, customize or personalize your shopping experience, and analyze the use of our Site and solutions to make them more useful to you. These technologies also allow us to aggregate demographic and statistical data and compilations of information, which may or may not include Personal Information, and provide this information to our service providers.  

Most Internet browsers allow you to remove or manage cookie functions and adjust your privacy and security preferences.  For information on how to do this, access the “help” menu on your Internet browser, or visit <http://www.aboutcookies.org/how-to-control-cookies/>.  Please note, however, that disabling our cookies may result in your inability to take full advantage of all of the features of the Site. To manage Flash cookies please visit [Adobe’s website](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html).    

**Analytics** :  We use analytics providers such as Google Analytics to help us evaluate and measure the use and performance of our Site.  To opt out of the aggregation and analysis of data collected about you on our website by Google Analytics, visit <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout> and download and install the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on.

**3\. Information We Obtain from Third Party Sources**

We may receive additional Personal Information from third party sources that we may append to existing consumer information, such as email and mailing address verification.  We use this supplemental information to better understand our consumers, deliver relevant offers and advertising, and improve our operations, stores, Site and our advertising and marketing campaigns. 

**4\. Location Information  **

We may collect location information through the Site so we can offer you certain location-based services (such as delivering advertisements that are relevant to your particular location, and conducting analytics to improve our stores and the Site). 

We may use various technologies, including IP lookup, to detect your location so that we can automatically show you the closest store to your area, rather than some random location. Depending on browser type, your browser may inform you that the website would like to collect your location and request your permission to do so. If you allow it, location information is then collected and may be stored locally on your device. If you decline the collection of location information, your location is not collected and you must manually enter your location.

### **Additional Uses of Personal Information**

In addition to the uses described above, we may use your Personal Information for the following purposes:

  * Operating our business, delivering our products and services, and for any other lawful, legitimate business purposes; 
  * Contacting you to respond to your requests or inquiries;
  * Providing you with newsletters, articles, product or service alerts, new product or service announcements, savings awards, event invitations, and other information;
  * Contacting you about programs, products, or services that we believe may be of interest to you, or sharing with you special offers from other companies;
  * Providing you with personally tailored coupons, programs, promotional information, offers, and other information;
  * Conducting market research, surveys, and similar inquiries to help us understand trends and customer needs across product categories or customer groups;
  * Evaluating your shopping experience or existing products and services, or to create new items;
  * Alerting you about a product safety announcement or recall or correction of an offer, promotion, or advertisement;
  * Administering sweepstakes and promotions or contacting you regarding a contest prize;
  * Preventing, investigating, or providing notice of fraud, unlawful or criminal activity, or unauthorized access to or use of Personal Information, our website or data systems; or to meet legal obligations;
  * Enforcing our Terms of Use and other agreements.

### **How We Share and Disclose Personal Information**

We share your Personal Information with third parties only in the ways described in this Privacy Policy.    

**Service Providers:  **We share your Personal Information with third party service providers who complete transactions or perform services on our behalf or for your benefit, such as for website hosting, administering the Smart Shopper Club program, marketing, analytics, processing employment applications and performing human resources administration, or to verify customer data, such as mailing addresses.

**Legal Process, Safety and Terms Enforcement:**  We may disclose your Personal Information to legal or government regulatory authorities in response to their requests for such information or to assist in investigations. We may also disclose your Personal Information to third parties in connection with claims, disputes or litigation, when otherwise required by law, or if we determine its disclosure is necessary to protect the health and safety of you or us, or to enforce our legal rights or contractual commitments that you have made. 

**Business Transfers:** Your Personal Information may be disclosed as part of a corporate business transaction, such as a merger, acquisition, joint venture, or financing or sale of company assets, and could be transferred to a third party as one of the business assets in such a transaction. It may also be disclosed in the event of insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership.  You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on any affected website of any change in ownership or uses of Personal Information, as well as any choices you may have regarding Personal Information about you.

### [**Your Ad Choices**  ](http://youradchoices.com/)

We support the self-regulatory principles of the Digital Advertising Alliance (“ **DAA** ”).   We work with a variety of advertisers, advertising networks, advertising servers, and analytics companies (“ **Ad Partners** ”) that use different technologies to collect data about your use of the Site (such as pages visited, ads viewed or clicked on)  in order to deliver relevant advertising.

These technologies may include the placement on our Site of cookies or web beacons, and other data collection technologies by these Ad Partners to track how our Sites is being used, to track where users go and what they do after their leave our Site, and to link various devices you may use, and to serve you more relevant ads.  These advertisements may appear on our Site or other services that you visit.

For more information about how Ad Partners use the information collected by the technologies on our Site and about your options not to accept cookies placed by some of these companies on our Site, please visit the [DAA’s opt-out page](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/). You may also opt out of additional third party advertising networks by going to the Network Advertising Initiative’s [website](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) and following the directions.

The opt-outs described above are device- and browser-specific and may not work on all devices.  If you choose to opt-out through any of these opt-out tools, this does not mean you will cease to see advertising.  Rather, the ads you see will just not be based on your interests.  In addition, when you opt out using one of these methods, our Ad Partners will continue to collect information for any other purpose permitted by the DAA’s rules.   You can opt out of future information collection from our Site by ceasing use of the Site.

Please note that this Privacy Policy does not cover the practices of our Ad Partners. Save-A-Lot does not have control over these third party technologies or the information contained in them.

### **Children’s Privacy**

Our Site is not directed to, and we do not intend to, or knowingly, collect or solicit Personal Information online from children under the age of 13.  We encourage parents or guardians to participate in and monitor their children’s online activity.  If a child under 13 has provided Personal Information to us, we encourage the child’s parent or guardian to contact us (see the “ **Contact** ” section below) to request that we remove the information removed from our systems.  If you are under the age of 13, do not provide us with any Personal Information either directly, on any website bulletin boards, or by other means.

### **How To Access or Update Your Information**

You may review your Personal Information that is readily accessible through our Site or contact us to request that it be updated. If you receive emails from us, you can update your information by clicking the “Preferences” link in any email we have sent you. If you do not receive emails from us, you can update your information by using the information in the “ **Contact** ” section below. We will retain your Personal Information for as long as reasonably useful for commercial purposes. We will retain and use your Personal Information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations or data retention policies, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.

### **Links to Other Websites**

For your information and convenience, our Site contains links to websites operated by third parties. Our Site also includes features like buttons and widgets hosted by other companies (for example, the Twitter “Tweet” button). These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our Site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. This Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we are not responsible for, the practices of third parties that collect your Personal Information. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of those third parties to learn about their information practices.

### **Updates to the Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy is subject to occasional revision, and if we make any material changes in the way we use your Personal Information, we will notify you by sending you an e-mail to the last e-mail address you provided to us and/or by prominently posting notice of the changes on the Site and updating the effective date above.

Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective upon the earlier of thirty (30) calendar days following our dispatch of an e-mail notice to you or thirty (30) calendar days following our posting of notice of the changes on the Site. These changes will be effective immediately for new users of our Site.

Please note that at all times you are responsible for updating your Personal Information to provide us with your most current e-mail address. In the event that the last e-mail address that you have provided us is not valid, or for any reason is not capable of delivering to you the notice described above, our dispatch of the e-mail containing such notice will nonetheless constitute effective notice of the changes described in the notice.

If you do not wish to permit changes in our use of your Personal Information, you must notify us prior to the effective date of the changes that you wish for us to delete your Personal Information. Continued use of our Site, following notice of such changes shall indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes.

### **Managing Communication Preferences**

If you have provided us with your contact information, we may send you email messages, direct mail offers, or other communications regarding products or services.   At any time, you may elect to discontinue receiving commercial messages from us by submitting an opt-out request to the contact information below or by following the instructions in the form of the communication you received, as described below.

To opt out of receiving marketing materials via email, please send an unsubscribe request to the email address below or click on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the email that was sent to you and follow the directions on the resulting web page.

### **How To Contact Us**

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or other privacy-related matters, you may contact us in the following ways:

**Mailing Address** :

Save-A-Lot

Attn: Marketing Department

100 Corporate Office Drive

Earth City, MO 63045

**Email Address** : [savealothelpers@savealot.com](mailto:savealothelpers@savealot.com)

**Phone Number:** 1-888-725-4537
